

<u>kara.malec@gmail.com</u>

O Graz, Austria

+43 67764873794

Profile

I am a junior Creative User Experience and UI Designer with substantial front end programming skills. In 2022 I decided to shift my career from Architecture to UI UX Design. Architecture is knowing how people interact with their environment, making it similar to UX design career.

My passion is for all forms of digital interface and the interaction it affords between a brand and a customer. I can work with you from conception through delivery or help complete projects you have already started.

Employment History

Architect, Atelier Thomas Pucher, Graz, Austria

January 2022 — Present

Project Manager, Energotechnika Engineering, Gliwice, Poland

October 2020 — September 2021

Architect, JSK Architekci, Warsaw, Poland

July 2017 — September 2020

Architect Assistant, Energotechnika Engineering, Gliwice

September 2015 — July 2017

Architectural practice, KWK Promes, Katowice, Poland

May 2015 — September 2015

Architectural practice, RARE architecture, London

June 2013 — June 2014

Education

Masters Degree in Architecture, Silesian University of Technology, Gliwice, Poland

September 2011 — May 2017

Architecture, Univesita di Bologna, Cesena

January 2013 — January 2014

One year Erasmus programme

Links

Portfolio Website (html & css)

Courses

Freecodecamp course, self-learner

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop HTML CSS Languages Polish English Italian German

Hobbies

Kitesurfing, Sailing, Snowboarding